[
  {
    "question": "Alma Thomas’s Snoopy is BEST described as",
    "a": "large and monochrome",
    "b": "realistic and textured",
    "c": "colorful and abstract",
    "d": "detailed and geometric",
    "e": "smooth and dynamic",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alma Thomas’s Snoopy connects",
    "a": "the civil rights movement and the first pictures of sunspots",
    "b": "global fears of climate change and Thomas’s teaching experiences",
    "c": "Thomas’s childhood experiences and the first moon landing",
    "d": "a city’s beautification and the first pictures of the earth from space",
    "e": "the conservationist movement and a famous solar eclipse",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the same time as her “Silueta” series, Ana Mendieta made outdoor artworks in",
    "a": "Caracas, Venezuela",
    "b": "Oaxaca, Mexico",
    "c": "Choloma, Honduras",
    "d": "Bogota, Colombia",
    "e": "Havana, Cuba",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following materials does NOT appear in Ana Mendieta’s “Silueta” series?",
    "a": "gunpowder",
    "b": "plastic",
    "c": "stones",
    "d": "cloth",
    "e": "grass",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ana Mendieta’s “Silueta” series examines",
    "a": "the fragility of nature",
    "b": "the devastation of war",
    "c": "female influence on the earth",
    "d": "the impermanence of humanity",
    "e": "her Cuban heritage",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rebecca Belmore became the first Indigenous person chosen to",
    "a": "represent Canada at the Venice Biennale",
    "b": "curate an exhibition at the National Gallery of Canada",
    "c": "win the Turner Prize for Contemporary Art",
    "d": "receive the Governor General's Award in Visual and Media Arts",
    "e": "have a one-person exhibition at the Whitney Museum",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following pieces did the performance art movement MOST influence?",
    "a": "Flint is Family",
    "b": "Unmoored",
    "c": "Speaking to their Mother",
    "d": "Snoopy",
    "e": "the Silueta series",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Speaking to their Mother toured the United States and Canada on the anniversary of",
    "a": "the Battle of Little Bighorn",
    "b": "the Kanesatake Resistance",
    "c": "St. Clair’s Defeat",
    "d": "Christopher Columbus’s landing in the Americas",
    "e": "the Yellow Creek Massacre",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Both Speaking to their Mother and Flint is Family address the issue of",
    "a": "clean water access",
    "b": "gender inequality",
    "c": "social inequality",
    "d": "immigration",
    "e": "climate change",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two of the following pieces are interactive for viewers?",
    "a": "Revival Field and Snoopy",
    "b": "Unmoored and Flint is Family",
    "c": "A Notion of Family and See-Saw",
    "d": "the Silueta series and See-Saw",
    "e": "Speaking to their Mother and Unmoored",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following artworks showcases a linguistic playfulness in its title?",
    "a": "Unmoored",
    "b": "Revival Field",
    "c": "Fundred Project",
    "d": "See-Saw",
    "e": "In the Name of Place",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "With which of the following statements would Mel Chin MOST agree?",
    "a": "Ecological problems do not require expensive solutions.",
    "b": "Large-scale earthworks are best at creating social change.",
    "c": "An artist’s background is the biggest influence on their work.",
    "d": "Art should be a two-way conversation between artist and subject.",
    "e": "Earthworks should not alter their environment.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Frazier’s A Notion of Family is MOST notable for its",
    "a": "critiques of pollution",
    "b": "odd camera angles",
    "c": "emotionally-charged scenes",
    "d": "photo album design",
    "e": "lack of color",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following artists believed MOST in developing a relationship with their subjects?",
    "a": "Mel Chin",
    "b": "Ana Mendieta",
    "c": "Rebecca Belmore",
    "d": "Latoya Frazier",
    "e": "Alma Thomas",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following descriptions BEST matches LaToya Frazier’s second act in Flint Is Family?",
    "a": "Shea and Zion Cobb move back to Newton, Mississippi.",
    "b": "Latoya Frazier stands alongside protestors advocating for clean water.",
    "c": "Shea and Zion Cobb stand outside a banquet hall.",
    "d": "Flint citizens drink clean water from a new atmospheric water generator.",
    "e": "Latoya Frazier stands outside of the Flint City Hall.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  }
]